myself so tandan I'm vice president for
health agency so we take care of Health
Products so recently we talked about the
Elevate product that we have launched so
there are the four major features about
the product that I will again brief you
so infinite care was one where in
customer can take an x amount of n
number of amount of claim in his once
once in his lifetime then was a power
booster we can wherein his policy
actually uh gets doubled every year so
if he buys a 10 lak policy it becomes 20
lakhs the next year this is again an add
on cover in next 10 years a 10 lak
policy will become a 1 CR policy and so
on and so forth right third was the jump
start that we talked about where in a
customer if he has a ped so he can get
the cover from 31st day as in the normal
policy if you see to it PD has different
different uh somebody covers it in two
years some covers it in three years with
jump start it it gets covered in 31st
day only then there was a unlimited some
insured uh addon feature that we had
where a customer can buy unlimited some
insured policy so these are the major
features that we have in our product
apart from these features we have some
18 add-on covers that a customer can buy
depending upon his needs so we had got
in a modular CHC product right wherein
if a customer needs some of the other
addon he can pick and choose and he can
uh get a premium and get his policy done
so now it's totally dependent on the
customer see again this product is again
based on AI that we talked about so
we'll actually give customer an added
Advantage we'll recommend him a plan
this is the best suited plan for that
particular customer so if depending upon
the demography depending upon his family
size depending upon what age he is into
right depending upon his income
everything so we'll curate a plan for
him and we will recommend a plan to that
customer so these are the major features
that we have launched in this product
what is the main reason to launch to
launch this product so main reason is
that we want to see again if you see
today India as a uh country we are only
we have only 5% penetration in health
insurance space so we want to grow we
are already number one in all other
segments we want to be number one in
health space as
well what's the present Market what the
f so q1 if I talk about uh is 2.9%
market share in health space and overall
health this is retail health I'm talking
about 2.9% and overall health space if
we see uh taking into comes and the
group business as well so we are at
11.4%
and see we as an organization want to be
at the
top
sorryy PD so basically see that is
called a jump start feature wherein
there are five lifestyle diseases so
there is asema there is obesity
hypertension hyper lipemia so all these
diseases are taking into C these are
called lifestyle diseases so if a
customer op for that jump start add-on
cover he starts getting his ped covered
pre-existing disease covered from the
31st day if he doesn't take that cover
it is a threee waiting period in the PED
if he takes that cover it comes down to
31 days
only is all including cancer no only
five lifestyle diseases obesity
hypertension hyper lipidemia asema